Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Schenectady County, 1948-2008; 4; 6.88 cubic ft.
  - Schenectady County, Super '74, Schenectady County Chamber of Commerce [Booklet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady County, A Survey of Local Government Services and Structure…, 1978 December (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schenectady County, Title 9 Economic Adjustment Strategy (1 of 2), Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Schenectady County, Title 9 Economic Adjustment Strategy (2 of 2), Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County, Topography, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1968 April (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schenectady County, Transportation, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1968 May (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady County, Wastewater Facilities Study [Informational Brochures], Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Schenectady County, Water Resources, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1967 December (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Schenectady County, Water Supply Plan Abstract Contract No. DACW 52-71-C-001 SMSA No.12, 1970 March (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady County, Welcome to Schenectady County, [Tourism Brochure], Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady County, Zoning for Solar Access and Solar Equipment in Schenectady County, 1981 March-1981 June (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - [Village of] Scotia, Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1967 November (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [Village of] Scotia, Planning Study, 1966 April (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - [Village of] Scotia, Summary of Village of Scotia Town of Glenville Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Capital District, 1936-2008; 5; 6.22 cubic ft.
  This series contains files pertaining to planning decisions for areas/projects that span county boundaries within New York State's Capital District -- i.e., Albany County, Rensselaer County, Saratoga County, and Schenectady County. A great many of the files involve regional transportation planning and travel data; this includes corridor plans and studies, as well as non-state federal-aid streets and highways conditions reports. There are documents pertaining to the Port of Albany spanning several decades. Other documents of note include an analysis of the Albany-Schenectady-Troy housing market, air quality data for the region, and a soil map of Albany and Schenectady counties from the 1930s.
  - Capital District, 1988 Regional Transportation Plan Report, 1988 February (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Capital District, 1989 Regional Transportation Plan Report, 1989 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Capital District, Air Pollution Capital District, 1968 March (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Capital District, Air Quality Implementation Plan Capital District and Town Catskill, 1978 December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Capital District, Albany Area Industrial Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Capital District, Albany County Airport Area Traffic Assessment, 1990 March (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Year Ended June 30, 1970, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Year Ended June 30, 1971, 1971 July (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Year Ended June 30, 1972, 1972 August (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Year Ended June 30, 1973, 1973 September (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Year Ended June 30, 1974, 1974 November (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Years Ended June 30, 1975 and 1974, 1975 August (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information Years Ended June 30, 1976 and 1975, 1976 July (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information June 30, 1977 and 1976 (Revised), 1977 October (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information June 30, 1979 and 1978, 1979 October (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information June 30, 1978 and 1977, 1978 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Albany, New York, Financial and Operating Practices July 1, 1975-January 31, 1979, Audit Report, 1979 December (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Annual Budget, Fiscal Year July 1, 1979 to June 30, 1980, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Budget, July 1, 1980 to June 30, 1981, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Financial Statements and Other Financial Information June 30, 1980 and 1979, 1980 August (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Master Plan Report (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Master Plan Report (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Capital District, Albany Port District Commission Master Plan Report (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Capital District, Albany, Rensselaer and Schenectady County Solid Waste Management Feasibility Study [Request for Proposal], 1988 March (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Capital District, Albany Shaker Road Corridor Study, [Draft Summary Report], 1979 February (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Capital District, Albany Shaker Road Corridor Study, Summary Report, 1979 September (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Capital District, Albany Shaker Road Corridor Study, Technical Report, 1979 September (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Capital District, Analysis of Development Potential of the Port of Albany, 1970 July (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Capital District, Analysis of Development Potential of the Port of Albany 2nd Phase Work Program 1969-70, 1970 August (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Capital District, Analysis of the Albany-Schenectady-Troy, New York Housing Market as of September 1, 1972 (1 of 2), 1973 February (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Capital District, Analysis of the Albany-Schenectady-Troy, New York Housing Market as of September 1, 1972 (2 of 2), 1973 February (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Capital District, Analysis of Year 2000 Congestion Levels in Critical Corridors of the Capital District Technical Report, 1993 October (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Capital District, Annual Planning Information, BLMI Report No. 85, 1978 June (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Capital District, An Application for Funding … "Comprehensive Health Planning and Public Health Services Amendments of 1966", 1972 February (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Capital District, Appraisal of the Use Solid Waste is Supplementary Fuel in Power Plant Boilers, Capital District Region, 1974 May (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Capital District, Arts Activities in the Tri-Cities Area, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Capital District, Arts and Cultural Resources Directory for the Capital District 1978-79, 1978 May (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Capital District, The Arts and Museums [Technical Report], 1976 May (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Capital District, An Assessment of Need for Perinatal Services in the Capital Region, 1997 March (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Capital District, Attitudes Toward Prepaid Medical Care in the Tri-Cities Area, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Capital District, Basic Corridor Plan for Express Facilities, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Capital District, Bedrock Topography and Glacial Deposits of the Colonie Channel Between Saratoga Lake and Coeymans, New York, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Capital District, Business Fact Book Part 1-Business and Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Capital District, Capital District Energy Contingency Plan [Draft], 1983 January (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Capital District, Capital District Energy Contingency Plan [Revised Draft], 1983 August (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Capital District, Capital District Hudson River Corridor Study-Regional Study, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, Capital District Industrial Site Identification Report, 1988 November (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, Capital District Regional Indicator Report: 2003, Benchmarking Progress in New York's Capital Program (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Capital District, Capital District Regional Planning Commission Data [Newsletter], 1978 April (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Capital District, Capital District Regional Secure Detention Facility, 1979 July (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Capital District, Capital District Traffic Volume Report, [Draft Technical Report], 1984 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Capital District, Capital District Traffic Volume Report, 1985 April (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Capital District, Capital District Traffic Volume Report: 1989, 1989 September (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Capital District, Capital District Transportation Authority Annual Report, Fiscal Year 1969-1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, Capital Transportation Authority Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Capital District, Capital District Transportation Committee Agency Establishment Information [Various Documents], Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Capital District, Capital District Transportation Committee Status Report 1976, 1976 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Capital District, Capital District Transportation Study: Land Use Classification Manual, 1964 April (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Capital District, The Capital District Urban Fishing Program: Albany, Schenctady, Troy Areas, 1978 March (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Capital District, A Case for the Location of the Solar Energy Research Institute in the Capital District, 1975 December (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Capital District, City and Town Existing Character Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Capital District, Coastal Zone Management in the Capital District, Phase 2 [Technical Report], 1977 July (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Capital District, Commercial Access in New York State's Capital District: Problems and Strategies, 1989 November (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Capital District, A Comparative Look at Criminal Justice Data in Albany, Rensselaer, Saratoga and Schenectady Counties, 1982 April (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Capital District, Comprehensive Solid Wastes Planning Study, Volume 3 Summary Report, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Capital District Non-Federal-Aid Streets and Highways 1984, 1985 November (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Capital District Non-Federal Aid Streets and Highways 1988, 1989 November (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Capital District Streets and Highways 1983, 1984 July (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Streets and Highways 1985, Vol. 1 Summary Report, 1986 November (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Streets and Highways 1985, Vol. 2 Condition Ratings, 1986 November (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Capital District, The Condition on Non-State Federal-Aid Streets and Highways 1987, Vol. 1 Summary Report, 1988 October (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Streets and Highways 1987, Vol. 2 Condition Rating, 1988 October (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Capital District, The Conditions of Non-State Federal Aid Streets and Highways 1989, Volume 1-Summary, 1991 August (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Streets and Highways 1989, Volume 2-Condition Ratings, 1991 August (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Capital District Roads 1991, Volume 1-Summary Report, 1996 March (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Capital District Roads 1991, Volume 2-Condition Ratings, 1996 March (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal-Aid Capital District Roads 1993, Volume 1-Summary Report, 1996 March (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Capital District, The Condition of Non-State Federal Aid Capital District Roads 1993, Volume 2-Condition Ratings, 1996 March (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Capital District, Continuing Operations Plan (Prospectus) 1979-84, 1979 December (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Capital District, Continuing Operations Plan (Prospectus) 1985-90, Volume 1, 1985 September (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Capital District, Continuing Operations Plan (Prospectus) 1985-90, Volume 2, 1985 September (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Capital District, County Criminal Justice Profiles 1982-1985, Volume 4, 1987 April (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Capital District, Crisis in Open Space: A Challenge to the Capital District [Book], 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Capital District, Demographic and Economic Data for New York's Capital Region: Albany-Schenectady-Troy, 1988 July (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Capital District, Department of Environmental Conservation Notice of Public Hearing, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Capital District, Development and Transit: A Cooperative Venture, CDTA, 1982 January (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Capital District, Development of a Health System Agency for Northeastern New York, 1975 September (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Capital District, Directory of Human Service Agencies Providing Transportation in the Capital District, 1979 February (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Capital District, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement/Solid Waste Management Plan [Executive Summary], 1990 August (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, An Economic Development Strategy for the Capital Region, 1986 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, Elderly and Handicapped Transportation Study, 1977 June (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Capital District, Elderly and Handicapped Transportation Study, 1981 August (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Capital District, Employment Projections from the Leontief Interindustry Model Volume 1, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Capital District, Environmental Attitudes Among the Tri-City Population, 1976 April (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Capital District, The Erie Canal Way [Informational Brochure and Book], National Park Service, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Capital District, Evaluation of the Four Largest Sanitary Landfills in the Capital District, 1974 January (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Capital District, Feasibility Assessment for a Capital District Integrated Solid Waste Management System (1 of 2), 1989 April (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, Feasibility Assessment for a Capital District Integrated Solid Waste Management System (2 of 2), 1989 April (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Capital District, Feasibility Assessment for a Capital District Integrated Solid Waste Management Plan [Appendices], 1989 January (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Capital District, Feasibility Assessments for a Capital District Integrated Solid Waste Management System Appendices A-G, 1989 April (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Capital District, Fixed Guideway Transit Feasibility Study Physical and Operational Analysis/ Capital Costs, 1995 April (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Capital District, Fixed Guideway Transit Investigation Summary Report, 1995 July (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Capital District, Fuel Conservation/Fuel Emergency Contingency Plan, Technical Memorandum #1 and #2, Impact of Fuel Shortages on Transit Ridership/Strategies and Responses, 1979 May (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Capital District, Growing Together within the Capital District: The Report of the State Commission on the Capital Region, 1996 June (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Capital District, A Guide to Advancing Transportation Project in the Capital District, 1993 August (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Capital District, General Description of Composite Network Routes, 1968 October (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Capital District, Guide to Natural Areas of the Eastern New York Chapter of the Nature Conservancy, 7th Edition, 1980 March (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Capital District, A Handbook of Labor Statistics Albany-Schenectady-Troy Labor Area, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Capital District, Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, INC.-Grant Application and Application for Conditional Designation (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Capital District, Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, INC.-Grant Application and Application for Conditional Designation (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Capital District, Higher Education the Capital Region: An Overview of the Area's Academic Institutions, Programs, and Services, 1987 October (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Capital District, History of the Capital District Region (Draft), Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Capital District, Homelessness in the Capital District, 1985 September (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Capital District, Industrial Archeology in Troy, Waterford, Cohoes, Green Island, and Watervliet [Book], 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Capital District, Hudson Mohawk Industrial Gateway City Edges Final Report: The Preservation and Utilization of 19th Century Industrial Architecture in the Hudson-Mohawk Region, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Capital District, Hudson River Crossing Study [Final Report], 2008 February (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, Hudson Riverfront, Albany and Rensselaer Design Workshop [Brochure], Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, An Inquiry into the Needs, Conditions, and Status of Persons of Spanish Heritage Living in the Capital District, 1976 October (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Capital District, Inventory of Abandoned Railroad Rights of Way, Region 1, 1972 January (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Capital District, Joint Waterfront Revitalization Program, Town of Coeymans Albany County, Town of New Baltimore Greene County [Preliminary Draft], 1985 November (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Capital District, Land Use Data and Files, Capital District Transportation Study, 1967 August (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Capital District, Local Travel Parameters, 1990 July (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Capital District, Capital District, Master Plan for Outdoor Recreation for the Capital District, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Capital District, Municipal Recreation: Albany, Albany County and Southern Half of Rensselaer County, 1966 April (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, The National Register of Historic Places in New York State, 1976 June (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Capital District, The Nature Conservancy Guide to the Natural Area of the Eastern New York Chapter, 1977 November (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Capital District, New Visions [Executive Summary], Capital Transportation Committee, 1998 January (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Capital District, New York Route 5 Corridor Land Use and Transportation Study [Final Report], Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Capital District, Northway Corridor Study (Exist 1 to 10), [Draft Report], 1995 April (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Capital District, Northway Economic Impact Study, 1965 April (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Capital District, Options for Suburban Transit Services in the Capital District, Discussion Document, 1990 November (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Capital District, Park-and-Ride Lot Study, 1987 April (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Capital District, A Plan for Maternity and Pediatric Care for Northeastern New York, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Capital District, A Policy Maker's Guide to the Capital District Transportation Committee (CDTC), 1986 February (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Capital District, Political and Business Visitors' Guide to the Capital District, Empire State Report, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Capital District, Part 2000, Expanding the Reach of the Port of Albany/Rensselaer [Master Plan], Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany, Golden Anniversary Celebration 1932-1982 [Informational Booklet], Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Capital District, The Port of Albany, Its Regional Implications for the Capital District Region, 1968 May (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study [Executive Summary], 1988 March (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan And Development Study [Full], 198 March (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Report #1: The Study Context, 1985 February (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Report #2: Port Utilization, 1985 October (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study Report #3: Inventory and Condition of Facilities, 1985 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Report #4: Port Operational Institutional and Financial Circumstances, 1986 April (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Report #5: Future Port Use, 1986 May (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Report #6: Physical Facilities Evaluation, 1986 September (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Report #7: Recommended Implementation Plans, 1987 March (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Special Report: Port of Albany Leases, 1986 April (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Master Plan and Development Study, Summary [For Public Meeting], 1988 March (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany [Promotional Brochures], 1999 February (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, Port of Albany Report No. 2, Winter-Spring 1981, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, Rediscover Port of Albany [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Capital District, Priority Water Problem List, Region 4, 1991 September (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Capital District, Profile of People, Jobs and Housing, Business Fact Bank Part 2, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Capital District, A Proposal for Analysis of Development Potential of the Port of Albany, 1970 June (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Capital District, Proposal to the New York State Environmental Facilities Corporation for a Solid Waste Management Feasibility Study… [Appendices], 1987 December (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Capital District, Proposal to the New York State Environmental Facilities Corporation, Part 2-Cost and Contract, 1987 December (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Capital District, Proposed Sites for UDC Housing in the Capital District, 1971 December (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, A Prospectus for a Comprehensive Transportation and Regional Development Study in the Capital District, 1963 May (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Capital District, Re: Albany Rensselaer and Schenectady Counties Feasibility Study/ Generic Environmental Impact Statement Request for Proposal, 1988 March (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Capital District, A Recreation and Open Space Inventory Study for the Capital District Region, 1969 November (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Capital District, Re: Crown-Ikarus Articulated Buses, CDTA, 1984 March (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Capital District, Regional Transportation Plan Needs Analysis and Major Facilities Improvement Plan, 1981 December (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Capital District, Regional Transportation Plan Report, 1993 December (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Capital District, Regional Travel Data Report, 1984 June (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Capital District, Regional Travel Data Report, 1984 September (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Capital District, Regional Water Supply and Wastewater Disposal Plan and Program, 1971 July (Box 5, Folder 25)